{
    "subject": "resource/Vasa_IFK",
    "predicate": "property/no",
    "object": "2",
    "human_readable": "The number of Vasa IFK is 2.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9419730305671692,
            "question": "Is the number 2 significant in any way related to Vasa IFK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7966393232345581,
            "question": "What is the number of Vasa IFK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5817034244537354,
            "question": "How many teams are there in Vasa IFK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5462721586227417,
            "question": "Are there more than one Vasa IFK teams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5055419206619263,
            "question": "Is the number of Vasa IFK teams a singular or plural?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4863469898700714,
            "question": "Where might you find more information about Vasa IFK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46947556734085083,
            "question": "What does 'Vasa IFK' stand for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37964242696762085,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a team that might belong to Vasa IFK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3763148784637451,
            "question": "What type of organization is Vasa IFK likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17180092632770538,
            "question": "Does the number 2 have a special meaning in sports?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The number of Vasa IFK is 2.",
            "html": "dbpedia_249_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of organization is Vasa IFK likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_249_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a team that might belong to Vasa IFK?",
            "html": "dbpedia_249_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does 'Vasa IFK' stand for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_249_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_249_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_249_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_249_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_249_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_249_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_249_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_249_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_249_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_249_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_249_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text documents do not mention the specific number of players on Vasa IFK's roster.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about the number of Vasa IFK, and therefore cannot support or refute the statement \"The number of Vasa IFK is 2.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}